origami-instructions.com 2011-12-31

# Origami-Instructions.com Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors to Origami-Instructions.com is important to us. 

At Origami-Instructions.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. 

Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit Origami-Instructions.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

Log Files 

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.

The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

Cookies and Web Beacons 

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We use CPX Interactive Inc and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.

This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

DoubleClick DART cookies 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the[ Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).  

CPX Interactive is deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users.

Accordingly, we strictly adhere to all industry guidelines, and will continue to review and improve our privacy policy and procedures to ensure the safety and protection of consumer information. This Privacy Statement presents our privacy policy, including CPX Interactive's privacy practices for our web site. Below is information regarding CPX Interactive's commitment to protecting the privacy of Internet users.

Consumer Information

CPX Interactive uses one or more third party ad serving technology to serve ads at this site and at our clients' sites. In the course of delivering an ad to you, the third party ad serving party may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser and use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this non-personally-identifiable information used to serve ads to you, please [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Cookies and Opt Out

Like most Internet sites, CPX Interactive and its third party ad serving party uses "cookies" to enhance the Internet user's experience on the Web. Neither CPX Interactive nor such third party ad serving party uses these cookies to personally identify you in any way, and these cookies in no way damage your system or files.

What are cookies and how do they enhance your Web experience?

A cookie is a unique number that is assigned to you the first time you are served an ad. This number is stored in a file on your computer. For instance, cookies help ensure that you don't repeatedly see the same ad. Cookies can also help advertisers measure how you utilize an advertiser's site and the effectiveness of an ad. This information can then be used by advertisers to better cater to your needs. In other words, cookies help us deliver to you the types of ads in which you are more interested.

Although we believe that cookies help enhance your experience on the Web (by not repeatedly serving the same ads to you and delivering more relevant messages to you), neither CPX Interactive nor its third party ad serving party needs cookies to deliver ads to you.

Opt Out

If you do not want the benefits of cookies, there is a simple procedure that allows you to deny or accept this feature. In order to "opt out" of the benefits of cookies, you may either manually delete your cookies by following the instructions contained in the Help section of your browser, or you may [click here](http://ad.yieldmanager.com/opt-out).

Industry Efforts to Protect Consumer Privacy

CPX Interactive is committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Accordingly, we strictly adhere to all industry guidelines, including those established by the Direct Marketing Association. To review information regarding privacy practices on our CPX Interactive Web site, please click here. If you should have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement, please contact our Customer Services at contact@cpxinteractive.comThis e-mail address is being protected from spambots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it . We recommend that you periodically review this Privacy Statement, as CPX Interactive may update it from time to time.

Third Party Advertising

We use CPX Interactive INC and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.
